<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Jayaram Kancherla</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Jayaram Kancherla</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 21:37:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 21:37:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Epiviz Epiviz is a suite of tools and packages for interactive and statistical visualization of genomic data sets.
-</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Link to CV. (probably the most upto date)
Hi there! I am a faculty researcher/scientific programmer with the Center for BioInformatics and Computation Biology (CBCB) at the University of Maryland, College Park. I am part of the University of Maryland Institute of Advanced Computer Studies (UMIACS).
Research Experience  Faculty Research Assistant/Scientific Programmer University of Maryland, College Park January 2016 - Present
Working with Dr. Hector Corrada Bravo to develop interactive data visualization and statistical exploration tools for functional genomic and metagenomic data sets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faq/</guid>
      <description>This contains a list of questions I get asked through email or friends!  Disclaimer: These are based on my experience and should be taken as official response!
 Are International Students eligible for ORISE (OakRidge Science) Fellowships ?  International students can apply to most ORISE fellowships (unless the position is only for US citizens). If accepted, you will be required to change your visa to J1 - long/short term research scholar depending on the length of the position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/</guid>
      <description>A more comprehensive list of publications is available at ORCID and ResearchGate.
PUBLICATIONS  Kancherla J, Zhang A, Gottfried B and Bravo HC. Epiviz Web Components: reusable and extensible component library to visualize functional genomic datasets. F1000Research 2018, 7:1096 (doi: 10.12688/f1000research.15433.1) (*equal contribution) Justin Wagner*, Florin Chelaru*, Jayaram Kancherla*, Joseph N Paulson*, Alexander Zhang, Victor Felix, Anup Mahurkar, Niklas Elmqvist, Héctor Corrada Bravo; Metaviz: interactive statistical and visual analysis of metagenomic data, Nucleic Acids Research, Volume 46, Issue 6, 6 April 2018, Pages 2777–2787, http://doi.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>